Joseph Ayomiposi Odenike

90 Hackford Road, Lanesfield. Wolverhampton WV4 6BU irejoseph16@gmail.com 07452785451

Profile

A vibrant individual with working experience, skilled in administrative duties, proven to excel in a fast-paced environment, and equipped with the ability to efficiently maximize limited time. An active listener who gives his 100% to any and all tasks given. I am a goal-oriented individual willing to learn and add value wherever I find myself.

Education

01/2023 - 09/2024

The University of Wolverhampton, Msc Data Science

Wolverhampton, **United Kingdom**

Babcock University, BSc (Hons). Accounting

08/2017 - 06/2021 Ogun state, Nigeria

Kingsfield College, WASSCE 2017

2011 - 2017 Ikorodu, Lagos state, Nigeria

Professional Experience

04/2018 - 07/2020 Lagos state, Nigeria

Customer Service Representative, Mojec International Ltd

- Ensured customer received high-quality service.
- Maintained high levels of customer service, working quickly and effectively under pressure.
- Provided basic training for new recruits, interns, and also acted as interim supervisor for the training period which lasted 4 months.
- Responded to telephone inquiries and complaints following standard operating procedures.
- Maintained knowledge of company products to provide helpful suggestions and recommendations to customers.
- Assisted in sorting and filing hard copies of financial transactions.
- Aided in postings of financial transactions unto sage 300.
- Engaged in filing and postings of petty cash transactions.

05/2019 - 08/2019 Abuja, Nigeria

Volunteer Tutor, Stella Maris Nursery and Primary School

- Helping children feel successful by giving positive feedback and support.
- Extending or supporting the literacy learning that happens within the classroom.
- Offering individual or small group attention.
- Acting as cover for tutors during absences to keep class orderly.

01/2022 - 11/2022 Lagos, Nigeria

Management consultant Intern (Advisory), *Price WaterhouseCoopers (PwC)*

- Prepared financial statements for several clients including a non-profit organization.
- Member of a team that performed bank reconciliation for a client in the process of acquisition.
- Drafted reports, Letter Of Engagement, using PowerPoint and Microsoft word.
- Part of a small team that was outsourced to assist a clients recruitment process.

- Maintained frequent interaction with senior management to measure goal achievement and determine areas of improvement.
- Conducted quality, timely performance feedback and performance appraisals.

05/2023 – present Birmingham, United Kingdom

Casual event staff, Compass group

- Ensure legal age compliance with alcohol purchases.
- Till cashier.
- Stock taking before and after events.
- Restocking work area.
- Ensuring a neat and tidy work area.

09/2023 – present Wolverhampton, United Kingdom

Teaching Assistant (1:1), Pine Green Academy

- Work with students to make sure they understand the lessons taught.
- Observe, record, and report the progress of students or a student in 1:1 situations.
- Assist lesson tutors to maintain a focused and engaging learning environment.
- Assist teachers in completing learning activities when required.
- Support teachers in managing class behavior.
- Help with outings and sport events.
- Assist with organizing and clearing away learning materials/devices before and after lessons.
- Guide 1:1 to designated areas when they need to take their space or engage in given task.

Watching movies

Assist in calmly deescalating tense situations amidst pupils.

Skills

Time management		Python		• • • • •
Customer service orientation		Relationship building		
Effective communication in written and verbal formats		Microsoft office suite proficiency Microsoft word, excel and PowerPoint		
Ability to work and function in a team Html, Css & Javascript		Sage 300 Basic knowledge of sage 300 React		
Certificates				
BSc (Hons). Accounting Second Class Honours (Upper Division)	Jobberman Soft-Skills Training		Safeguarding & Prevent	
MSc Data Science				
Interests				

Video games

References

Sports

Made available upon request